<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<ResearchProjectDef Name="GF40K_ResearchBase" Abstract="True">
		<tab>GF40K</tab>
		<techLevel>Ultra</techLevel>
		<requiredResearchBuilding>HiTechResearchBench</requiredResearchBuilding>
		<requiredResearchFacilities>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumWeaponry</li>
		</requiredResearchFacilities>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_ImperiumCore</defName>
		<label>Imperial technology</label>
		<description>Unlock the secrets of the enigmatic Weaponry Cogitator Node, a specialized module designed to interface with the advanced research table and delve into the ancient armament technologies of the Imperium of Man. According to the sacred beliefs of the Mechanicus, all cogitators are imbued with a highly intelligent Machine Spirit, though never reaching the realm of true Artificial Intelligence. The Weaponry Cogitator Node embodies these sacred principles while empowering your researchers to explore the vast realm of weapon technology, guiding your colony towards unrivaled advancements in the art of war.\n\nWith this research completed, the doors to unparalleled armament knowledge shall open before you, leading to the development of advanced weaponry that will forever change the course of your colony's battles. Forge a path towards supremacy on the battlefield, for the Omnissiah watches over those who seek knowledge in the pursuit of victory.</description>
		<baseCost>4000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>AdvancedFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<requiredResearchFacilities Inherit="False">
			<li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
		</requiredResearchFacilities>
		<researchViewX>0</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularMelee</defName>
		<label>Imperial melee weapons</label>
		<description>Delve deep into ancient combat techniques and experimental designs to unlock the secrets of Power Swords, Power Sabres, Chainswords and Eviscerators. Harness the raw might of these deadly close-combat weapons, each with unique features and devastating strikes. With this research, your colony will gain access to a formidable arsenal of advanced melee weapons, arming your warriors with the cutting edge of close-quarters combat. Turn the tide of battle in your favor and dominate your foes with unmatched precision and lethality.</description>
		<baseCost>4000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularMeleeForce</defName>
		<label>Imperial force weapons</label>
		<description>Unravel the enigmatic mysteries of psionic power and martial prowess with the Force Weaponry Research project. Delve into the ancient texts and technological blueprints to unlock the secrets of Force Halberds, Force Staves, and Force Swords. Master the art of infusing weapons with psychic energy, and learn how to harness the raw power of the mind in melee combat. With this research, your colony will gain access to advanced force weaponry, allowing your skilled warriors to become formidable psychic warriors on the battlefield.</description>
		<baseCost>5000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_RegularMelee</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>2</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<!--ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularMeleeMechanicus</defName>
		<label>Adeptus Mechanicus weapons</label>
		<description>Embark on a journey into the secrets of the Adeptus Mechanicus with the Mechanicus Arsenal Research project. Study the sacred tomes and rediscovered schematics to uncover the blueprints for Arc Mauls, Omnisian Axes, Mechanicus Power Swords, Taser Goads, Transonic Blades, and Transonic Razors. Unleash the power of the Omnissiah in your hands as you forge these powerful melee weapons. With this research, your colony will possess a formidable arsenal of Mechanicus melee weapons, striking fear into your enemies and defending your lands with the blessings of Mars.</description>
		<baseCost>6000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_RegularMeleeForce</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>3</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef-->

	<!--ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularMeleePersona</defName>
		<label>Melee (Persona)</label>
		<description>PLACEHOLDER</description>
		<baseCost>4000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0</researchViewY> 
	</ResearchProjectDef-->

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularStub</defName>
		<label>Stub weapons</label>
		<description>Delve into the ancient texts and rediscover the sacred art of Stub Weaponry. From the merciless thunder of the Stub Shotgun in close-quarters battles, to the steady roar of the Stub HMG, laying waste to your foes at medium range. The Stub Carbine and Pistol, symbols of precision and tenacity, will hold their own against any foe, their high stopping power a testament to their craft. And in the hands of your expert marksman, the Stub Sniper, a weapon of unmatched accuracy and deadly finesse, will deliver death from afar.</description>
		<baseCost>2000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularArc</defName>
		<label>Adeptus Mechanicus weapons</label>
		<description>Embark on a journey into the secrets of the Adeptus Mechanicus weaponry. Study the sacred tomes and rediscovered schematics to uncover the blueprints for Arc Mauls, Omnisian Axes, Mechanicus Power Swords, Taser Goads, Transonic Blades, Transonic Razors, Galvanic Rifles, Arc Pistols, and Arc Rifles. Unleash the power of the Omnissiah in your hands as you forge these powerful weapons. With this research, your colony will possess a formidable arsenal of Mechanicus melee and ranged weapons, striking fear into your enemies and defending your lands with the blessings of Mars.</description>
		<baseCost>9000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.00</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>


	<!--ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularRangedArc</defName>
		<label>Adeptus Mechanicus arc weapons</label>
		<description>Embark on a pioneering research project to unravel the enigmatic mysteries of Arc Weapons. Delve into the arcane technology that powers the fearsome Galvanic Rifle, Arc Pistol, and Arc Rifle. These legendary firearms harness the power of electrical force and are revered for their ability to deliver devastating shocks to both flesh and machine. Through this research, your colony will gain access to the formidable and electrifying Arc Weapons, ensuring your enemies will tremble before your might.</description>
		<baseCost>7000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef-->

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularRangedPlasma</defName>
		<label>Imperial plasma weapons</label>
		<description>Uncover the arcane knowledge of channeling superheated energy into devastating plasma projectiles. Explore the mysteries of Plasma Pistols and Plasma Guns, weapons that can melt through enemy defenses with unparalleled ferocity. Master the volatile power of plasma weaponry to turn the tide of battle in your favor. Through this research, your colony will wield the scorching might of plasma arms, capable of obliterating even the most formidable adversaries and unleashing havoc upon the battlefield.</description>
		<baseCost>6000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.70</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularRangedBolter</defName>
		<label>Imperial bolt weapons</label>
		<description>Uncover the ancient art of crafting and utilizing devastating firearms that fire self-propelling 0.75 caliber explosive projectiles. These weapons are capable of discharging powerful explosive rounds, tearing through armor and rending foes asunder. Unleash the thunderous fury of Bolt Pistols, Bolt Guns, and Bolt Snipers upon your enemies. Through this research, your colony will gain access to a versatile and lethal arsenal of ranged weaponry, perfect for annihilating your foes and asserting dominance on the battlefield.</description>
		<baseCost>5000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.40</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularRangedLaser</defName>
		<label>Imperial las-weapons</label>
		<description>Unravel the secrets of harnessing focused energy beams to pierce through enemy defenses and deliver swift justice. Develop advanced Las Weapons like the Long-Las, Lascarbine, Lasgun, Laspistol, and Las SMG. With this research, your colony will wield firepower capable of searing through armor and incinerating adversaries with blistering precision. Embrace the power of laser technology and usher in a new era of ranged combat superiority.</description>
		<baseCost>4000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.95</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GF40K_ResearchBase">
		<defName>GF40K_RegularRangedSpecial</defName>
		<label>Imperial special weapons</label>
		<description>Embark on a unique research journey to unlock the secrets of Special Weapons - the legendary Flamer and Grenade Launcher. These rare and exceptional firearms possess extraordinary abilities that set them apart from conventional weaponry. The Flamer engulfs foes in cleansing fire, while the Grenade Launcher rains down explosive destruction upon your enemies. This research will grant your colony access to the pinnacle of special weaponry, capable of turning the tide of battle with unmatched versatility and awe-inspiring force.</description>
		<baseCost>6000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
		  <li>GF40K_ImperiumCore</li>
		</prerequisites>	
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>4.55</researchViewY> 	
	</ResearchProjectDef>
</Defs>
